♫ In the not too distant future
♫ Way down in Deep 13
♫ Dr. Forrester and TVs Frank
♫ Were hatching an evil scheme
♫ They hired a temp by the name of Mike
♫ Just a regular Joe they didn't like
♫ Their experiment needed a good test case
♫ So they conked him on the noggin
♫ And they shot him into space
♫ Ah
♫ We'll send him cheesy movies
♫ The worst we can find
♫ He'll have to sit and watch them all
♫ And the monitor is mine
♫ Now keep in mind Mike can't control
♫ Where the movies begin or end
♫ He'll try to keep his sanity
♫ With the help of his robot friends
♫ Robot roll call Cambot,
Gypsy, Tom Servo, Croooow
♫ If you're wondering
how he eats and breaths
♫ And other science facts
♫ Just repeat yourself it's just a show
♫ I should really just relax
♫ For Mystery Science Theater 3000 ♫
(electronic robotic tones)
- Hi everybody, your
local Mike Nelson here.
Say listen, I've programmed the robots
to have different
regional speech patterns.
(chuckles)
Okay, I admit, it's the
only thing I know how to do
but still it should be fun to
try to watch them communicate,
don't you think?
- So Croooow, before we go to the show,
would you all like to have a Coke?
- Ah sure, I'll have a root beer.
- I said Coke.
- I know, I'll have a root beer.
- All I have is Coke.
- Then forget it, I'll
just use the bubbler.
- Okay, huh?
- Oh by the way, what show are we seeing?
I thought we were going to a movie.
- We are.
- And a show?
- No.
- Then why did you say
we're going to a show?
- Because we are.
- What show?
- Awakening.
- That's a movie.
- I know, geez!
Are you gonna come with?
- Come with what?
- Me Croooow, me!
Are you gonna come with me?
- Yeah, but I'm a little low,
could you borrow me some money?
(chuckles)
- Wait a minute, okay,
I think that's enough.
You know, there's a
difference between regionalism
and just plain stupidity.
- But Mike, irregardless of that fact...
(playful pop music)
- So what time's dinner?
- Is noon okay?
- But that's lunch.
- Lunch, dinner, same thing.
Oh something's flashing
over to the what's it area.
- Oh the blinker.
- Oh yeah.
(yawns tiresome)
- Ah Mike, oh, oh, what time is it?
Uh, I slept late.
I have an experiment for
you around here some...
Frank? Where's the matter
transference device?
- When did you use it last Clay?
(sighs)
- Oh uh here it is.
Well this little device allows you
to break down molecular patterns
and reassemble them again elsewhere.
I haven't gotten all the
bugs worked out of it yet.
I thought I'd try it out on you.
- You know, there's a bit of an ion storm,
are you sure you should
be sending that right now?
- Nonsense, what could possibly go wrong?
(sighs)
(high-pitched whirl)
(groans out)
- Get me rocket number nine.
(electronic buzzes)
- So we're not gonna do any experiment
that messes with the laws of nature,
you try your little
matter transference device
out on your own self.
- Yeah, you're just lucky nothing happened
sending it up during an ion storm.
(chuckles)
- Yeah, what he said.
(laughs maniacally)
- What the hell?
- What in the world?
- You failed to properly
compensate during the ion storm,
your agonizer please.
- But Captain Mike!
- Your agonizer, please.
- Agonizer, agon, where the heck did I put
that do hickey?
- It's right there on your belt.
- No, no, that's not it.
- It is too!
- Nope, I remember I had it--
- Would you just give
me your agonizer please?
(electronic whirls)
(chuckles evilly)
Oh for crying out loud,
you're supposed to keep
fresh batteries in your
agonizer at all times.
- I don't know what happened, I just put--
- Well that's just, hey!
- [Croooow] fresh ones in.
- Let's just go to the agony booth,
it's just easier.
- [Croooow] It's being cleaned.
- It is not.
- Tom? What's happened?
What's wrong with Mike and Croooow?
- Uh, what do you mean?
- I mean they're all evil and stuff.
- Really? I hadn't noticed.
- Well don't you think
it's just a little weird
that we're down here in deep 13?
- Yeah that is weird, still I suppose
they do that kinda thing.
- Tom, it seems as though the ion storm
sent us into an evil parallel dimension,
our lives are at stake.
We can't trust anyone.
- Well okay, let's just
try to make the best of it.
- Oh typical, agony booth is out of order.
Ha, you can call those service people
and they'll be around,
oh say, December maybe.
Well I can bring it out to be six months--
- Shut up you old man crow.
- Shutting up, thank you.
- Your movie today is
a little western called
The Last of the Wild
Horses that I like to think
smells like the inside
of John Goodman's chaps.
(laughs evilly)
Yippy die-yi-yah.
(laughs maniacally)
Shut up.
- And this one here, (chuckles)
is the eight of Chris Lemon.
- Oh will you look at that?
(chuckles)
(buzzer buzzes)
- [Both] We've got movie sign.
(gasps panicked)
- Let it go, let it go.
(electronic tones)
- [Voicoever] Last of the wild horses--
- [Frank] Aren't you gonna
carry me into the theater?
- [Clay] Frank, you're
getting too big for that.
- [Frank] Oh, it's my favorite part.
- [Clay] Just watch the show,
I have that siatic nerve...
- [Voiceover] This is
the Road River Valley
in Southern Oregon, famous for its scenic
and historical landmarks.
- [Frank] Like dirt and stuff.
- [Voiceover] Oregon's
first settlers stopped here
and built one of the oldest settlements.
- [Clay] Then they moved on.
- [Voiceover] Whose original
buildings still stand
as when they were built
nearly a century ago.
- [Frank] Wow.
- [Voiceover] The entire
action of this picture
was filmed in the
beautiful Road River Valley
and in Jacksonville,
one of the few remaining
true western towns.
- [Frank] So even though the movie sucks,
they still had well...
- [Clay] Can't stress that enough folks,
Last of the Wild Horses.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Frank] Freezee...
- [Clay] With these people
and plenty of vitamins and minerals.
(actionable orchestral music)
- [Frank] You lost the last
of the wild horses, you dink.
- [Clay] Oh Albert Glasser,
the man who holds you down
and pummels you with music.
I wonder what day Albert
Glasser wrote this score.
(mumbles)
Two curlies fighting for supremacy.
- [Frank] I would date Yolanda Molinari,
she seems nice.
(powerful orchestral music)
- [Clay] My life as a
dog, the western version.
- [Frank] I never wanted
to do summer stock
in the first place.
- [Clay] Oh yeah, the
Hittleman film empire
began with this movie.
- [Frank] Let's save our strength,
they'll probably have to
fight later in the movie.
Oh don't, oh...
(chuckles)
- [Clay] Little Joe and Adam have it out.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Frank] Hey I have leather contacts!
- [Clay] You rarely see
a good facial whipping.
- [Voiceover] In the first place Bonham,
now I'm going to finish you.
(whip cracks)
- [Frank] Journey to
the beginning of time.
- [Clay] Scrubbing bubbles,
scrubbing bubbles, oh!
- [Frank] Hey, he's
dressed like a car sack,
what is that about?
- [Clay] We're not moving
here, look at all the people.
- [Frank] Ew, smells
like grandma's purse, ew.
- [Clay] It's the bazooka Joe guy.
(gun fires)
- [Frank] Hey, I had dibs.
- [Clay] Down, down boy, shoo, go home.
- Looks like kind of a one sided caper.
- [Clay] You're good boss.
- Well, it's none of my business.
- [Clay] I don't even know who I am yet.
(actionable orchestral music)
- [Frank] I hope it's not the three amigas
'cause I think of comedy.
- [Clay] Yeah.
(actionable orchestral music)
Oh man, a great big juicy stage coach!
(gasps eagerly)
Oh getting horse sick, (groans).
I hope you know that these
are billable hours boss.
- [Frank] Boss, you
care too much, damn you!
- [Clay] No, stay, go home, go home, go!
(suspenseful orchestral music)
Duty freckles, no, go home.
(actionable orchestral music)
- No use hanging on to
that artillery any longer,
might as well get rid of it.
- [Clay] See your license please?
- I mean now.
- [Frank] Oh yeah, their three guns
are probably useless against his one.
- What are you butting in for?
- Three against one isn't exactly
my idea of the right odds.
- I don't know who you
are, but you're not gonna
get away with this.
- [Frank] I'm a bunny!
- There are horse thieves we were chasing,
there's a law about aiding
and abetting a horse thief.
- Oh well now why didn't somebody tell me?
Far be it for me to break the law.
- [Clay] He's being facetious isn't he?
- [Light Jacket Cowboy] I
thought he was an honest citizen,
and you fellas were breaking the law.
- [Frank] Apparently sarcasm
hasn't hit the old west yet.
- I guess he must be over the hill by now,
no use chasing him, might as
well call the whole thing off.
- [Clay] To-mah-to!
- [Frank] Tomato!
(imitates steady beep)
(chuckles)
I still got it.
(imitates car engine revs)
(gun shot fires)
- [Clay] Oh God, that stang!
- [Frank] Way to go Ted, now
we have to talk to him again.
- [Clay] Please sir, can
we have our bullets back?
- There oughta be a law against the man
who carries and can steal weapons.
You boys get tempted too easy.
Get down.
- [Frank] This is very
awkward 'cause all the horses
are really good friends.
- [Clay] It's pretty embarrassing.
Now line dance!
- Take 'em off or I'll burn 'em off.
- [Frank] Now ask 'em if you can
show 'em something in a new buck pump.
- [Clay] Let me help you here Gary,
you had those hammer toes.
- [Frank] Foot fetishes of the old west.
- [Clay] Now say you're
going to check in back
for a size five.
- Drop 'em.
- [Frank] Did I say throw them?
Now do it again.
- [Clay] They're all wearing white clogs.
(playful orchestral music)
(chuckles)
- [Clay] Hey, you've got flat toes.
- [Frank] I miss my spur noises.
- [Clay] Jacksonville,
where church, family,
and hopefully someday
industry, come together,
great big backs of the old west.
- [Frank] Oh no, he just hit a pedestrian.
- [Clay] I'm so sick of
gingham, I could scream.
(chuckles)
I love my job.
- How was the trip.
- We were almost held
up over near the pass.
- Yeah? What do you mean almost?
- I'm carrying a big shipment,
I wasn't taking any chances.
I was watching the road
ahead about half a mile
and I seen this mass parts,
by the time we got around
the bend, he was gone.
- All right, we'll try and round him up.
Get the horses Chuck.
What'd he look like Tom?
- Oh he was a big fella, his own horse,
had a black bandana.
- [Frank] Beautiful thighs.
- That's good enough for me, see ya later.
- [Frank] Nice tummy.
- Go help Mrs. Bigsby and Mrs. Jones.
Now look, everything
is gonna be all right,
break it up folks, break it up.
- [Clay] Go on home and
disappoint your husbands.
- [Frank] Ew, look at the all poo.
(groans in disgust)
Whoop, one of my tires is low.
(slow orchestral music)
(air bursts jokingly)
I will not let you not buy this shoe.
(chuckles)
- [Clay] I couldn't help, that tickles.
- [Frank] I wasn't playing shoe store!
- [Clay] You know, his horse has the look
of someone who spent a lot
of time humoring his master.
- [Cowboy] Hello there!
- [Frank] Hello there!
- I just had a little trouble.
My horse threw a shoe.
- [Clay] Ate a ringer.
- Oh that's too bad.
I think you can get him
reshot up at the ranch.
- Which ranch?
- Double C.
- Oh that's fine. Where is it?
- [Frank] What an idiot.
- You're on it, covers
practically the entire valley.
- [Frank] And most of the world!
- The ranch house is up over
the next hill about a mile.
- Thanks.
Say, it's lucky for me you happened along,
otherwise I mighta had to walk.
- I got news for you,
you're still gonna walk.
- [Clay] Yippe-yi-ouch!
Oh good one boss!
Maybe I could just hold
on to your horse's tail
and you could drag me
or something, I dunno.
- [Frank] The Double
Cranch? What is that about?
It's a sprawling studio apartment ranch.
- Who's Jane bringing home with her now?
- [Frank] How do you like this one dad?
- Hello dad.
- [Dad] Hello dear.
- [Frank] Hello dear.
- Why sure he can have
a shoe for his horse,
we got more shoes than we have horses.
- [Clay] Dad's mental.
- Four legs to one horse, hey Slim,
go and shoe this fella's horse.
- Thanks.
- You look like you could
stand something cool and wet.
- [Clay] Dad!
- I sure could, so could my feet.
- [Frank] Get his feet
a glass of lemonade.
- Well don't just stand
there, go get us a drink.
- Yes dad.
- Get on this Remy.
♫ Dah da da da da
♫ Dah da da da da dah ♫
- I like the property you got around here.
- [Clay] Real dysfunctional.
- Yeah built it all up myself,
started from scratch with
a brood of wild mares.
Never would stop expanding
if it hadn't been for this.
- [Frank] Oh well now I'm expanding, ha!
- I got in a stampede one night
and bust myself up good.
Ever since then, I turned over most
of the management to Riley.
- [Clay] Oh that's nice,
where's your daughter?
- Must be a lot of wild
horses in this part
of the country.
- No, no (mumbles).
- [Frank] His doppleganger.
- Couple?
- From the small ranch owners,
they claim that we're the cause of it,
that we're taking too
many mares from the herd.
- Ah let them claim whatever they want.
- [Clay] Tourette's of the old west.
- They don't like it, they know that...
- Looks like you're the one
who could use something cool now.
- [Frank] Hi I'm Susan,
I'll be your daughter today.
- [Clay] Oh quit giving me pee.
(upbeat pop music)
(playful orchestral music)
- [Clay] Curly and anti-Curly.
- Afternoon Miss Jane, Mr. Cooper, Riley.
- Well sheriff, what brings you here?
- Oh I'm trying to pick
up a fella's trail.
(mumbles) just pulled into Jacksonville
a little while ago and
reported seeing a mountain man
down to the big gun (mumbles).
- Sit down sheriff.
- Thanks Jane.
- [Frank] That's a long sentence
and you're probably tired.
- Howdy.
(mumbles)
- No, we had a couple extra guys
planting the coast.
The guy riding on the seat
was watching the road ahead
for about a half a mile
through field glasses.
- [Clay] Fascinating.
- By the time they got to the pass,
the masked men had gone.
- [Clay] It's me.
(coughs) It's me.
- I sure woulda liked to seen the look
on that fella's face if he'd have tried
to stick up that stage.
(chuckles)
- [Frank] The joke is on the sheriff.
- Did the guard get a good look at him?
- Yeah as good as you could
from a half a mile away
through field glasses.
Said he was big, was wearing
a black bandana for a mask,
and riding the wrong horse.
- [Clay] Well actually,
my scarf is dark navy
and so is my horse.
- I (mumbles) your job sheriff,
this country must be full of big fellas
wearing black bandanas
and riding around horses.
- [Frank] Everyone here is so fun!
- No, not so many.
- [Clay] Say, you got a
sweet outlaw ass, don't you?
- You're big.
Unless I'm mistaken, that's a
black bandana you're wearing.
- [Frank] They are falling
for each other hard.
- What kind of horse was
this man riding Mr. Cooper?
- [Frank] It was just a head and a stick,
it was weird!
- A roan.
- [Frank] I could explain,
it was a loaner roan.
- Something wrong sheriff?
I wasn't near the pass.
I came up through the valley.
- [Frank] Let's go barefoot all summer.
- [Clay] Yep well that's just me,
I gotta have an art support in a firm.
- Come on, give me your gun.
- [Frank] Well, they'll do that sometimes.
- Well I guess my horse
outta be shot by now,
thanks a lot Mr. Cooper.
- Freeze.
- [Frank] Oh, they're playing freeze tag.
- What's this all about Rocky?
- Every shot Hank?
He made us get off our horses,
stampede them, and then took our guns.
- Took your boots too I see.
- [Frank] Shut up Iris.
- What have you got to say for yourself?
- Part of what he says is right.
- [Clay] Yeah, them
other part is right too.
- They just thought I'd be laying a little
and give the kid a break,
but he took a shot at me.
- [Clay] I'm so lost.
- I don't like any unnecessary gun play
going on in my jurisdiction.
You're gonna have to answer
to a charge of assault
and that just places you down at the pass,
which is another a little
matter I wanna get cleaned up.
Let's go.
Put it away Rocky.
- [Clay] Yeah and we're gonna
pin the cattle wrestling
from last year on you
too, if you don't mind.
- [Frank] He's wearing chick jeans,
they fit better!
He drank our apple juice.
- (mumbles) close enough to tell for sure.
- I suppose you took a
couple of pot shots at them?
- Well yes, but we were
only trying to scare him--
- Haven't we got enough
trouble in this valley
without my men making more?
- [Frank] No.
- Riley, get him out of my sight
before I have him thrown off the ranch.
I warned you before Rocky
about being trigger happy.
- I wanna talk to you.
- [Clay] Glad we had this
little face to groin talk.
- I told you to be careful
whenever you made a move,
next time you go after anyone,
be sure there are no witnesses around.
- This fella came out of nowhere.
- Well watch your step from now on.
Things are going too good to spoil.
I got the old man so he won't budge.
- [Clay] I put a rock behind his wheel.
- I want you to push the
small ranchers around
until they won't take anymore,
when they're pushed too far,
this whole valley will burst loose.
- When that happens, where do we stand?
- Oh the sidelines.
- [Frank] Uh, what's the sideline sir?
- When they do, we'll bring
the lower down on them,
(mumbles) they're wiped
out, I'll take Cooper.
- Suppose old man Cooper got
his own idea about all this.
- When I get through with him,
he'll see things my way or else.
- [Frank] Why did he hire a (mumbles)?
- Because you got braun
where your brains outta be.
You stick with me and you'll
be wearing gold bullets.
- Where? In my belt or my back?
- [Clay] Why if this
scene wasn't ending I'd...
Oh.
♫ Bless your beautiful hide ♫
They need to invite the stop light.
- Remedy, there he is!
- [Clay] Stop the music.
(joyful orchestral music)
- [Frank] Retail space for ads, see?
(playful orchestral music)
- This town has a real western feel.
- [Clay] I'm going to
crab tree and leveling.
- [Frank] I'm strangely drawn to him,
the magnetic pull is too strong!
- [Clay] Wanna go have
a beer before I book ya?
- [Frank] I like to greet him at the door
wearing nothing but this.
- What's the charge?
- Oh the charge?
Assault with intent to
kill, he shot Hank Davis
and one of the Double C boys.
- That's right?
Me and Tara was right
there, saw the whole thing.
It was self defense,
Hank drew first and fired
before he even got his gun out.
- [Woman] Hank fired four shots.
- Two.
- Sounded like four to me.
- [Frank] Oh forget it, you weren't there.
- I've been having trouble
with my ears lately.
- Yeah, so there I am on
(mumbles), just like--
- [Frank] You're not gonna
be in this movie are you?
- Remind me to fix up
some of that ear remedy
when we get back to the ranch.
(mumbles)
- Your word's all right with me Remedy.
- [Clay] Even though you're mental.
- I guess that sort of clears you
of the shooting, doesn't it?
- [Clay] Thank you.
- But I'm gonna hold
you on another charge.
- What kind of a charge?
- Suspicion.
A description of the masked man
waiting to hold up the
stage, fits you pretty well.
- He ain't the man you're
looking for sheriff,
he was with us every single day.
Wasn't he Terry?
- Never left my side for a second.
Why he's no more than
crook than you are sheriff.
- [Old Man] Why he's the new ranch hand
I hired the other day.
- Well I guess that clears you
all the around, doesn't it?
- [Clay] Well it's easy going justice
'round these here parts.
- [Frank] Yep.
- Thanks for the help.
(mumbles)
- Hey Remedy?
- Yeah?
- [Sheriff] I wanna talk to you a minute.
- Wait a minute--
- [Frank] Oh this is gonna be great!
- [Clay] Can I show you
something in a slip on,
maybe open toed, something
sensible, nothing too...
- I just wanna remind you
that you were right here
when the stage pulled in and
reported the whole thing.
- Me?
You must be suffering
with that double vision
I was talking about, if you
are I got a remedy for it.
(chuckles)
- [Clay] Oh my trick nipple!
- But I'll tell you
what I'm willing to do,
I'm willing to place him in your custody
until I'm satisfied one way or the other.
- Oh, he'll come to a (mumbles).
- [Clay] God love the drunken old fart.
(chuckles)
- [Frank] Hey, they got in
a shipment of muslim women.
- Thanks pal.
- Don't mention it.
(mumbles)
That makes us even.
- That's quite a kid you got there,
plenty of nerves,
plenty of what it takes
to ride a horse too.
- [Clay] Harassment!
(chuckles)
- Well what do you know? A little tom boy.
Say if I'd known that, I
wouldn't have sacked her--
- I tell her 100 times,
if she's gonna go 'round
dressed like a boy, she's gotta
learn to take it like a boy.
- [Frank] Oh!
(mumbles)
- Barnum, Duke Barnum.
- [Frank] I think.
- Well I guess I'd better take off.
- Take off?
- Yeah, I've got a sort
of a state over equipment.
- [Clay] I'm opening a shoe store there.
- Maybe?
- So long Remedy.
- Oh it ain't gonna be so long.
- As far as I'm concerned it is.
- But you're supposed to
be our new ranch hand.
- Oh you made a mistake.
- [Frank] But you're my love interest!
- Well maybe he did, maybe
I better go tell the sheriff
he ain't the man I hired the other day.
- [Cowgirl] Yeah, must've been
a case of mistaken identity.
- [Farmer] Yeah.
- Funny though, he looks just like that--
- [Clay] Everybody wants
a piece of the Duke.
- You got a bad memory for faces.
- [Frank] Who are you?
- You better take another look.
Am I the fella that Remedy hired or not?
- [Frank] You're the
jerk that smacked my but.
- [Clay] Oh we gotta go, let's go.
(mumbles)
(metal clangs)
- Hey I've got this puppet,
let's do a song about the lemur.
- Okay!
♫ Joey the lemur, the friend to mankind
♫ Offering kinda monkey friend
♫ He really does shine
♫ Joey the lemur, he's
great to have around ♫
(gasps out)
- This is worse than I ever imagined
having my worst nightmare about.
- This is horrible, there
are no lemurs in this movie!
(screams out)
♫ The lemur, the kind of animal
that would go the bathroom ♫
- Oh no, no, now wait a minute...
- It's the lemur.
(mumbles)
(static buzzes)
- I order you! Let me go!
You traitorous pigs.
What's going on? Where's
my personal guard?
(chuckles)
Oh right Mike, whatever your game is
I'll play it mister.
- Apparently some sort of
transposition has taken place.
- Extremely interesting plankton,
I have no idea why I said that.
- Anyway, we gotta get
him inside the theater.
- What is it that will buy you?
Power? I can get that for you.
Money? Credit? Name it!
Name it!
(upbeat pop music)
- [Tom Sirvo] Let me go!
- [Croooow] Would you just--
- [Tom Sirvo] Die, I'll have you killed,
and then tortured.
(inaudible argues)
Oh hey, a cowboy movie.
- [Mike] That's right, just and watch it.
- I've seen everything, what do you study?
- Oh just a little of everything,
cure anybody of anything,
man or beast, medicine, I have back cream,
(mumbles), veternarian--
- [Croooow] Victoria's Secret?
- Number 40, now I can pull that tooth
that's been bothering Curly.
- [Tom Sirvo] My butter shipment.
- No the (mumbles).
- Don't tell me you're
studying to be a dentist too.
- Why, you got a toothache?
- No thanks.
- [Croooow] I want to be a dentist.
- So that's why they call you Remedy, eh?
- Yep.
Sure there's nothing wrong with you?
- No, I'm disgustingly healthy.
- [Tom Sirvo] And I'm not gay.
(ominous music)
Hey, there's a drug deal going down.
- I'll be with you in a few minutes.
I've got a little unfinished
business to take care of.
- [Croooow] I need to get really drunk.
- Don't go out of your
way looking for trouble.
- I won't go out of my way.
- [Croooow] Wow, this place is crawling
with holly hobbies.
- [Tom Sirvo] What kinda drink specials
they got in there partner?
Hi!
- I want to correct something you said
at the Double C a while ago.
- [Croooow] You used a double negative.
- I've never shot a man in the back.
- [Tom Sirvo] Kidneys sure, but...
- I'm gonna give you a
chance to eat those words.
- [Croooow] Hey, the 2
o'clock shoot out's starting!
Could we have some privacy please?
- Suppose that I won't?
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh I never thought of that.
- [Croooow] I hope this doesn't ruin
the taste of Jacksonville festival.
- I'm gonna give you a
chance to draw first.
- [Tom Sirvo] Sale at Penny's!
- [Croooow] Oh the Amish
are really hauling ass.
- [Tom Sirvo] Wonkiest couple
of cowboys I've ever seen.
- [Crooow] As my legal representative,
what would you recommend?
Uh so uh, what are you gonna do now?
- Well?
- All right, all right.
- [Tom Sirvo] Have your way baby.
- As far as I know, you never
shot anyone in the back.
- [Tom Sirvo] Well thank
you, that's all I wanted.
- That's better.
- [Croooow] That's worse!
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- Drop it!
- [Croooow] Wow, pistol packing mama!
- [Tom Sirvo] Ha, saved by a girl.
Stupid, you scuffed my hair you dink.
- [Croooow] He's wearing Adam Ant's shirt.
- Shoulda known better
than to turn my back...
- [Tom Sirvo] I've learned
an invaluable life lesson.
- [Croooow] They're always
gathering for fights,
how do they ever get any shopping done?
- Handy with his dukes too.
- Maybe that's how he got his name.
- [Croooow] His name is Handy? Or Wiff?
It's a town of carry nations.
- [Tom Sirvo] Is this
like Gamro versus Zikra?
Only with cowboys?
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Croooow] Cool, he almost
made it into his hat!
- Break it up, break it up.
Get up now there Watkins.
There's a law in this town
against disturbing the peace.
(chuckles)
- You got a lotta laws around here.
- [Tom Sirvo] I'll say.
- Yeah and I aim to see
you don't break any.
- Come on Duke.
- [Tom Sirvo] This is a
pretty wimpy old west.
- [Croooow] It's more
like the mid-west part
of the old west, like Des Moines.
(sweet orchestral music)
- [Tom Sirvo] Remedy's
other nickname is ow!
- What a beautiful cut.
- [Croooow] Have you
ever thought of a perm?
- Of course I could
probably have done the job
with only two stitches,
no use taking chances.
- No.
Besides, you needed the practice.
- [Tom Sirvo] You get your
greasy thumb outta there.
- Got a professional look too!
You know, I can hardly see it.
Wouldn't know I done it
myself if I hadn't done it.
- Will he be all right Remedy?
- Course he will.
- [Croooow] You'll be able
to think in a month or so.
- You got a fever?
- No, but I think you have.
- [Croooow] Remedy, soon
to be known as Malpractice.
(chuckles)
(sweet orchestral music)
- Quite a girl you got there.
- [Tom Sirvo] Well here,
take her for a drive.
- She's sort of left with
me when my partner passed on
15 years ago.
- Oh I see.
- No, times could (mumbles).
- [Tom Sirvo] Fascinating.
- I know when I'll grow old.
(laughs boisterously)
- [Croooow] I've been trapped by this guy
at so many parties.
- I don't see why you dragged me out here.
The size of this place, it looks as though
you could run it with the
help you've already got.
- Oh I know it ain't a very big place,
but I sort of figured if you
were as handy with horses
as you are with--
- [Croooow] Hey, what's he looking at?
- You might get to like it.
Stick around, raise the horses,
instead of sticking up stage coaches.
- [Tom Sirvo] I need some
alone time right now.
- What makes you think I
wanna make a career of it?
- [Tom Sirvo] I'm just a dilitante.
- How many you stuck so far?
- Oh, not counting the
one I started today, none.
- I thought so.
- [Croooow] You're right perty--
- No one with a crooked streak in him
would stick his neck the
way you did this morning.
- [Tom Sirvo] Well here
comes wacky, nutty, chaos.
(chuckles)
- [Croooow] Oh my comic
relief shift is over.
(mumbles)
- Oh even (mumbles) hurts it.
- That's what you get
for eating the old cooks.
- [Tom Sirvo] Yo, why don't
you blow it our your...
Oh Remedy.
- Open your mouth.
I don't need a shoe horn,
open your mouth, wider.
- [Croooow] Here's your problem,
you got a tongue stuck in here.
- There it is, the third bicuspid.
- No it ain't, my tooth.
- [Croooow] Now my mouth
tastes like your foot.
- [Tom Sirvo] I'll just disinfect this
by wiping it in my armpit.
- [Croooow] Rochester, what
a nice picture, oh, oh.
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh, I'm all
full of knits, spiders,
(groans out).
- Yes sir Curly, chew anything,
you gotta get through it.
- [Tom Sirvo] There's devils inside you.
- What's the root of
all this horse trouble
in the valley, Remedy?
- Lack of horses, they'll
come sooner or later I guess.
He's taken the mares
away from the wild herd,
pretty soon there's no more herd.
- What's the solution?
- [Tom Sirvo] Saline!
(chuckles)
- In the lumber country when
the forests start to go bad,
they stop cutting trees for a while,
that's what we gotta do here,
stop rounding up horses from the wild,
maybe a year or two, give the
herd a chance to grow old.
- [Croooow] Look, I'll pull my tooth.
- Everybody in favor of it?
- Everybody but the Double C.
- Charlie Cooper?
- Well he can stand one bad year
better than us little fellas.
So far, he's been stubborn as a mule.
I'm afraid if he won't listen to reason,
trouble's gonna go a lot
deeper than just bad seasons.
- [Croooow] Now, let's
get that appendix out.
- That's too bad.
- [Remedy] It's a beauty Curly.
- Oh!
- [Remedy] Brand new,
never been used before.
- [Croooow] Are they allowed
to have two comedy people
in this movie?
- Maybe I better look up the literature
on how to use them?
No, I'll just waste some time,
just yank 'til something gives.
Open your mouth.
(groans out)
Come on, open your mouth.
- [Tom Sirvo] Is it safe?
(sweet orchestral music)
Wow, frontier dental hygenist.
(growls)
(screams out)
- [Croooow] Lay off the (mumbles).
- [Tom Sirvo] Dances with uh, something,
I'm not sure what, I dunno.
- [Croooow] Are we
supposed to find our smile?
We're file clerks, what the hell
are we doing on horses?
- [Tom Sirvo] Bin to the bum to the done
to the ban, bonanza!
Bonanza, staring the Mandrell sisters.
- [Croooow] They don't seem wild,
they seem more fancy free.
- The Double C don't let a day go by
without raiding the herd.
- [Croooow] I still like this
movie better than Silverado.
- [Tom Sirvo] Is this legend
of Curly Joe Juridas Gold?
- [Croooow] The three try captains
meet for the coin toss in
the middle of the field.
- Are they the wild horse?
Are they the bubble free stock?
- The answer is yes to both questions.
- [Tom Sirvo] Do you Arlene Francis--
- If you fellas don't lay
off that herd for a while,
there isn't gonna be any herd.
- [Tom Sirvo] That's what I heard.
- You make it a habit of butting in
to everything that's not
your business, don't you?
- Maybe I'll make it my
business from now on.
- We take our orders from Mr. Cooper.
If he wants horses, we round 'em up.
If you don't like it, take it up with him.
- [Tom Sirvo] Middle
management of the old west.
- [Croooow] Okay, see
you at card club then.
- This thing has gotta
be brought to a head
once and for all.
- [Tom Sirvo] And popped!
(chuckles)
(upbeat pop music)
That was a fun day.
- Hello Jane.
- Hello Sheriff.
- Mr. Cooper, how's things?
I had some visitors this morning.
- [Croooow] Oh we just painted that tree.
- A delegation from the other ranchers,
they wanna know once and for all
if you're gonna lay off
that wild herd for a year?
- What I said still goes,
nobody's gonna tell me
when I can and can't run horses.
- [Croooow] Dad, did you
need to yell at me again?
- Well I guess that's final then.
- That's final.
- [Tom Sirvo] Is it final?
- All right Mr. Cooper.
- [Tom Sirvo] That's final.
- But I'm warning you,
I won't be responsible
for what happens.
You know I only got one deputy.
You got a lot of ranchers.
- I'll protect my own range, I've got guns
and I've got the men too.
- Is that the only way you know how
to settle things with a gun?
- [Tom Sirvo] Shut up Iris.
- Those ranchers are
right and you know it.
- [Tom Sirvo] I tell you shut up.
- But rather than sacrifice anything,
you'll turn against me
who were your neighbors.
You shoot and kill men
who once were your friends
just to assert your will and your power.
- [Tom Sirvo] She speaks
for all women every where.
- If you want to, but remember,
you turn them against
you and you turn me too.
- [Croooow] Just for that,
I'm not gonna let you
feed me or help me with my ablushions.
- [Tom Sirvo] I do like
stuffing more than potatoes.
- Tell them the Double C won't
run any horses for a year.
- [Croooow] Excuse me, I'm
sorry, I didn't catch...
- I'll notify Riley and the boys.
- [Tom Sirvo] I'm sorry,
the sound and the music
is kinda--
- [Croooow] Yeah I didn't...
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh crap.
(sweet orchestral music)
- [Croooow] And now Robert Lipper pretends
he is John (mumbles).
- [Tom Sirvo] I think she
may be doing that wrong.
(chuckles)
- [Mike] She has no idea how delightful
her life's about to become.
- [Tom Sirvo] Huh? Oh geez, I
shoulda looked the other way.
Hi, it's me.
(chuckles)
- [Croooow] Her shorts should be shorter,
or her pants could be longer.
- [Tom Sirvo] Kind of grunge.
Oh, oh, sat on the saddle horn there.
(sweet orchestral music)
- Hello there!
- [Croooow] Hello there.
- My horse decided to jump fences,
he took the last jump without the saddle
and I happened to be in it.
- [Tom Sirvo] She can
really tell a story, huh?
(mumbles)
Oh, oh, oh!
- You can't!
- Why not?
You made me walk.
- [Tom Sirvo] Pay back time.
- But I don't know why I did it
and I felt awfully bad
about it afterwards.
- You felt bad about it?
I've got a couple of
blisters to prove how I felt.
- [Tom Sirvo] Wanna see 'em?
- Well I guess I can't blame you.
(sweet orchestral music)
- [Croooow] And to think I was
going to have sex with you.
- Hey wait a minute.
- Yes?
- [Tom Sirvo] I wanna see you crawl.
- I'll take your saddle.
- [Croooow] And your
goucho pants, come on.
Your feet hurt yet? How's it feel?
Keep walking sister, feel
every blister I felt!
(chuckles)
I like you!
- I knew you were a gentleman.
- Now I've been accused of everything
since I hit this part of the country.
- [Tom Sirvo] Shot Kennedy
according to some folks.
- Okay your honor, what's the sentence?
(sweet orchestral music)
- [Croooow] Hey, look
at that idiot over there
with the saddle.
(chuckles)
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh, rush hour,
the sun down slow down.
- You know it's funny.
(chuckles out)
- [Croooow] What?
- They seem to sense that it's safe
to come back into the valley again.
- [Tom Sirvo] Wanna drive for a while?
- Year's gonna make a lot
of difference in that herd.
Your father did the right thing
when he came to terms
with the other ranches.
- I wish I could make him see that.
Even though he did give in,
I still feel he regrets doing it.
- Well that's too bad.
If he doesn't keep faith,
the whole thing's liable
to blow wide open again.
- Don't worry about that,
once he's given his word
he'll keep it.
- That's good.
- [Crooow] That was a great scene,
oh back to the main scene.
Oh my head!
(sweet orchestral music)
- [Tom Sirvo] Yeah thanks for the help,
I've only been getting off horses
since I was five.
I'm a formula one race car, vroom, vroom!
- [Croooow] Oh he's not
gonna tell any of those
weird ass jokes, is he?
(chuckles)
- Every time I see you two,
you only got one horse between you.
(mumbles)
- I just saw her in the corral,
she decided to come home without me.
- [Tom Sirvo] Why don't you grab a shave.
- Thanks for the lift.
- Don't mention it.
Next time, it'll be your turn.
- Well, have you been
beating up or shooting
any more of my help lately?
- None today, so far.
- I hear that fight you
had in town was a honey.
I used to be able to handle
myself pretty good too
when I was your age.
- I'll bet you could.
- [Tom Sirvo] May I
look under your blanket?
- Say, Jane tells me you're not too happy
with the deal on the horses.
- You're darn right I'm not.
- [All] Yeah, wow.
- If it hadn't been for her, I
wouldn't have gotten into it.
Do you realize what
one year's inactivity's
gonna do to the Double C?
- [Duke] Well, it's gonna cost
the little fella something too.
But the end, you'll all--
- [Croooow] It's a talking wheelchair.
- [Tom Sirvo] Don Adams eavesdropping.
- [Mr. Cooper] I'll stick to it.
- [Duke] Glad to hear you say that,
otherwise there might be a fight.
- [Tom Sirvo] Every time they have fun,
they never invite me.
I thought they'd be planning
my surprise party, but no.
- [Croooow] Wow, he's black
crow leader singer thin.
(mumbles)
- [Tom Sirvo] I want you to find my butt.
- [Croooow] What?
- I want you to round up every wild horse
in Memford Valley.
- Are you kidding?
There's hundreds of them between here
and Papercut Mountain, besides
we haven't got enough men.
- I know that.
You'll have to take whatever
men we an spare from here
and pick up the rest out on the range.
Do you understand?
- [Tom Sirvo] I definitely
kind of understand.
- You know?
If we do that, it'll be the
last of the wild horses.
- [Croooow] And there will be no need
for Arthur Miller's misfits.
- [Tom Sirvo] Now, my butt, my butt,
I had it at church.
Look at those guys, they got butts.
I'm just sitting on my pelvis,
no flesh there or anything.
(playful orchestral music)
(chewy squishes)
- [Tom Sirvo] Ew, has his scalp
ever seen a bar of soap?
- Not bad!
- [Croooow] I'm sure I can lose the weight
before the wedding.
- Not bad at all.
I think Terry's gonna like it.
- It feels kinda tight.
- That's okay, Terry ain't as big as you.
- She's bigger in some places.
- [Tom Sirvo] Two grown
men ladies and gentlemen.
- You know, I think I'm
gonna have (mumbles)
my hands over the next two years.
I think I'll take a (mumbles).
- How come Terry decided she wanted
to dress like a girl all of a sudden?
- Well she's a girl ain't she?
- Yeah, sure, but, how come
she just got conscious of it?
- What makes a girl realize she's a girl?
A man, you fool!
- [Croooow] I want this scene to go away.
Thank you!
- Things are gonna be
pretty quiet for a while
around the ranch now
that everybody's stopped
rounding up horses.
- I've just been thinking
about the same thing.
- [Tom Sirvo] Do you visualize (mumbles)?
- Will you stay on anyway?
- I don't know, if Remedy wants me to.
- Then you'll stay.
Remedy said you can
make anybody do anything
he wants them to do.
He once took a course in will power.
(chuckles)
By mail.
- [Croooow] Actress, please
stay in the reflector light.
- Do you have a girl?
- [Tom Sirvo] No, I got me a horse.
- Oh sure.
- [Croooow] Uh, what's a girl?
- What's she like?
- Which one?
You mean that you have more than one?
- Well no, that is not
more than one in each town.
- [All] Liar!
- Get two girls together,
you know how women talk.
I'll never forget the one in El Paso,
or was it Albuquerque?
Well anyway, when these two girls got--
- Well I think you're terrible.
- [Croooow] Why thank you!
(chuckles)
- [Tom Sirvo] Here we
go, philandering bastards
of the old west.
- Yeah the movie's just starting
to mosey now.
(sweet orchestral music)
(upbeat pop music)
Geez Mike, Sirvo's gotten really weird
and Gypsy is too.
- Yeah I know, I'm afraid we've lost them
to an alternate universe.
- Oh yeah, that'll happen.
I suppose we oughta do something, huh?
- Yeah, of course we should
do something, and fortunately,
I saved my alternate
universe manual from college.
- You went to college?
- Well, actually it was a
votech, but still manuals are--
- Well we better go get it quick.
- Okay, good.
(chuckles erupt)
- It's a dangerous game
we play, Tom Sirvo.
- I know, you mean like jarts?
- No you fool, I mean
power, ultimate power.
- Oh yeah, right.
(chuckles)
- The power to rule the
galaxies, it's ours!
Yours and mine for the taking!
- No kidding? Wow!
(chuckles)
- Are you man enough to take command?
- Oh yeah I suppose.
- Are you sure?
- Well I don't know if I...
- Come here.
- Uh oh.
- And let me make a man
out of you, Captain Sirvo.
- Oh, wow.
(buzzer buzzes)
Oh geez, look it's movie siren,
sorry honey, gotta go!
- I will be a captain's woman!
(electronic swooshes)
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh, boy that Gypsy
is one sexy mama, isn't she?
- [Mike] Hey.
- [Tom Sirvo] Gypsy, I know.
- Chances are, they'll
be watching the pass.
Drive the herd toward the Double C.
- [Croooow] Double C?
I thought it was the Double Cranch.
- Don't worry I will.
- [Tom Sirvo] Here's a curling iron.
- Drop this where they'll
be sure to find it.
- [Croooow] I want you
to brand Carol Channing.
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom Sirvo] Good talking to
you Ernie, always a pleasure.
- [Croooow] Oh boy, I'm
galloping, no need to hit me!
(mumbles)
- [Mike] Occasionally,
you'll see one of them horses
at spa golf and wrap parties.
- There they are.
- [Croooow] Without
you Gary, we'd be lost.
- [Tom Sirvo] That's them.
- All right men, we know
the herd don't bother 'em,
but if there's any riders,
you know what to do.
- [Croooow] Uh actually we don't sir, sir?
- [Tom Sirvo] You see, this is where
the seepia tone really pays off.
- [Croooow] Drink in the lush photography.
- [Sirvo] Hey mind your space cushion.
(mumbles)
- Here they come.
- [Croooow] They showed that clip
at the Academy Awards when that guy
was nominated for best actor.
- [Tom Sirvo] On top of everything else,
they're litterers.
(gun shots blast)
- [Croooow] Hey, the
horses don't have guns!
- [Tom Sirvo] They're
quakers you bastards.
Paw, paw, paw, paw.
- [Croooow] Dow, dow, dow, da, da, dow.
- [Tom Sirvo] Da, da, dow.
How are they chucking M80s?
(gun fire blasts)
- [Crooow] And then it
just sort of peters out.
- Did you get post up,
follow any of those riders?
- [Tom Sirvo] Did you (mumbles)?
- Come on, we'll go down the Double C.
- Wait a minute, you haven't any proof
that it is the Double C
men other than the word
of some drunk.
He might have just been
shooting off his mouth.
- That's right, I'd hate
to see us make a move
without some kind of proof.
- So would I, but...
- Hey Ferguson, look what
I found in the meadow?
- The Double C branding
iron, convinced now?
- This settles it, let's go.
- [Croooow] So their whole
plan is based on dumb luck.
(upbeat suspenseful music)
Whoa Phil, you flamed out your horse!
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh hop
sing is making chow mein.
- [Croooow] This is a
gripping Levi's commercial.
♫ Hi ho
♫ It's off to work we go ♫
(door knocks)
- [Croooow] We've come a courting,
delivering their funds a popping.
- Hello Mr. Ferguson.
- We'd like to see your father Jane.
- [Mr. Cooper] Jane? Who is it?
- Ferguson dad.
- Oh hello Pete.
- [Croooow] Ow!
- Hi boys.
- [Croooow] Old man, your picante sauce
is made in New York City!
- I guess so, it's got Double C on it.
- It was found down in the meadow.
- I guess one of the boys, careless.
- Very careless.
- [Tom Sirvo] Wow, that's
like a whole foot of ear.
- What are you driving at?
- That iron was found down in the meadow
after some riders drove a
band of wild horses through.
- [Tom Sirvo] This is about me, isn't it?
- Well you're not insinuating
we've been raiding the herd?
- We're not insinuating anything Charlie,
we're just taking tabs.
- That branding iron might
have been lost a week ago,
a month ago, anytime.
- [Voiceover] Well that's possible.
In that case, you won't object
to our looking over your stock.
- You're darn right I object.
- Oh but now--
- I'm done with this.
- [Croooow] Sorry for lending my support.
- I told you the Double
C hasn't been raiding
the wild horses.
I don't propose I have
anybody inspect my stock
to check up on my word.
The whole thing's beginning
to look like a frame up.
I wouldn't be surprised
if one of you fellas
on the back of the whole thing
in order to break up the agreement,
'cause that's the way you want it,
that's all right with me.
- Well you said a thing
for silver Mr. Cooper.
(mumbles)
(Tom Sirvo grumbles)
- I'm giving orders, any trespassers
in the Double C will be shot on sight.
- [Duke] Mr. Cooper,
you're only buying yourself
a lot of trouble.
- I can pay for anything I buy.
- [Croooow] Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
- [Tom Sirvo] Kindergarten
baby, wash your face in gravy,
wrap it up in bubblegum, and
send it to the navy, nah.
- [Croooow] Hey come on, I was kidding!
Hey wait!
And they still had to pay parking,
the Double Cranch does not validate.
- I don't think you
realize what this means.
- Well they've left me no other choice.
- Look dad--
- No please Jane.
- [Croooow] Get the doomsday machine.
(ominous orchestral music)
- Riley!
- [Tom Sirvo] I wasn't listening!
- [Croooow] He's the George
Stefanopolis of the ranch.
- [Tom Sirvo] Snuffleofogus.
George Snuffleofogus.
- I just told Pete Ferguson and the boys
if there's any trespassers
on the Double C,
they'll be shot.
- [Croooow] Send out a press
release to that effect.
- Why not let the sheriff handle it?
- Those are orders Riley.
- Don't you see?
Then if they come on your ranch,
you'll have the law on your side,
you'll be entitled to protection.
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh once again,
I'm putty in your hands.
I'll go over here.
- I guess I lost my head.
Maybe that's the best way to handle it.
(mumbles)
- [Tom Sirvo] John Waters, Texas ranger.
- For a while last night, it looked as if
the whole thing was bust wide open.
- You know, I had a feeling
it wasn't gonna last.
- [Croooow] It was a great brunch though.
- Protection.
I can round up some men and swear 'em in.
- You won't have to look for any deputies.
- [Tom Sirvo] I hear
my rotisserie baseball.
- [Croooow] Let's see,
dear sheriff I like you,
do you like me?
Check one.
- These are Double C men.
- [Tom Sirvo] Double Semen!
(chuckles)
- [Croooow] Don't touch me.
- We're picking our own deputies.
- Not while I'm sheriff.
- [Tom Sirvo] Wait, I'll be right up there
and then I'll retort.
- Maybe we can do
something about that too.
- [Croooow] I'd love to bite
the bridge of your nose.
- Are you forgetting that
Cooper put you in this job?
- [Tom Sirvo] El
Demando's of the old west.
- Well what's it gonna be?
Our deputies or your job?
- [Croooow] So, is that
the end of the scene
or do you have another...
No that's it, okay.
- [Riley] Now remember, you're deputites.
- [Tom Sirvo] Why thank you.
- No matter what you do,
you got the law on your side
and if someone should
accidentally be killed
while resisting arrest, that's too bad.
- [Tom Sirvo] Huh, huh? Get it?
Kill guys!
- [Croooow] Can we do anything sir?
Can we burn puppies?
- Maybe this will come in handy
to settle some personal affairs.
- [Croooow] Now there's a man
who understands me, thank you.
- [Tom Sirvo] Now go do that
voodoo that you do so well.
- [Croooow] We got the law on our side,
I'm gonna fail to yield!
Woo!
- [Tom Sirvo] Give it up for my posse!
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Croooow] Uh guys, it's not as much fun
as I thought it would be.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Tom Sirvo] Hey don't push, I'm going.
(drums whimsically)
Now fly my horsies, fly!
(cackles evilly)
- [Croooow] I'm not leaving!
Just because the rest of you are doing it,
I don't have to.
Let's all go to Fort Lauderdale.
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh, blew a tire.
- [Croooow] I don't
think you're supposed to
burn your own barn Ted.
Well, quick cup of Joe, then back at it.
(imitates fart)
(chuckles)
- [Tom Sirvo] Funny!
- What do you want here?
- Just checking your horses to see
if there's any Double C
brands in your corral.
- Get off my place,
there's no Double C horses
in my corral.
- [Tom Sirvo] Then if you wouldn't mind
doing me the service of dying!
(gun shots blast)
- You're getting Double C horses now.
- [Croooow] If you were alive, you'd hear
that ironic retort.
The ton ton macoots of the old west!
- [Tom Sirvo] Old timer Billy Slater, no!
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Croooow] No, I don't
wanna live with grandma!
- [Tom Sirvo] This guy
wouldn't even be a greeter
at Roy Rogers.
- [Croooow] Hey, he transmigerfied.
He's thinner.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
You never liked him, neighbor declares.
- [Tom Sirvo] Building code
invented and under fire.
At least there's no Art Buckwald.
(hums whimsically)
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Croooow] Word exonerated is invented.
- [Tom Sirvo] Literacy rate rises to 1%.
- [Mike] Look at that,
the orcs are involved.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Croooow] Siamese horses.
- [Tom Sirvo] Dan Roan and Dick Martin
in Once Upon a Horse.
- [Mike] It was a great movie.
Wasn't it once fun?
- [Tom Sirvo] You guys,
we have the whole prairie,
do we have to bunch up like this?
- [Croooow] How many of you
already know about Amway?
- Remedy like us, were to join us.
- [Tom Sirvo] Plop, plop.
(plops erupt)
Howdy Hitler!
- I'm asking you to go back to your homes
and your ranches quietly.
- [Croooow] But I live in a trailer.
- Who's gonna answer for Ferguson's death?
- [Tom Sirvo] What'd he say?
Louder, can't hear you back here!
- Catch up with Ferguson's killer,
let the sheriff handle the Ferguson case,
pop violence isn't the answer.
- [Tom Sirvo] Who's
that guy way over there?
- [Croooow] Shy.
Flop drop at 10, pass it on.
- [Voiceover] How do we know
you ain't in Cooper's pay?
- No I'm not in Cooper's pay--
- [Tom Sirvo] But don't pick at that.
- I'm not gonna stand by and
watch a range war break out
if I can possibly help it.
- Clem, you're talking like a fool.
- [Voiceover] Cooper broke his word.
- [Croooow] Yeah pass
and we won't kill him.
- [Tom Sirvo] Yeah!
- He might listen to me.
He knows I don't own a ranch,
so I don't have nothing personal to gain.
At least let me try before you all
do something you might all regret.
Go on back to your
ranches, give me a chance
to talk to Cooper alone.
- [Croooow] Yeah, I got
it down at flea farm,
they had real good deal, they
were having a special on us.
- You know what he's saying is (mumbles).
Now why don't you all go home.
- [Tom Sirvo] See where Oklahoma
wants to be a state?
Can you believe that?
- [Mike] Now there are acid burns
all over this part of the prairie.
- [Croooow] Wait everybody,
this means we have to go home
to our wives.
- [Tom Sirvo] Shit.
- [Mike] Yeah look at those horse's asses.
(sweet orchestral music)
- I got your message.
- I want to see your father.
- [Mike] Well I hope you
two will be very happy.
- I only want to talk to him.
- [Tom Sirvo] Here's your power drill.
- I don't think he'll see you.
- Somebody's gotta make him
realize what's happening.
The small ranchers are up
in arms over the killing.
- [Croooow] So this isn't a date?
- I'd like to help, for your sake.
- [Mike] Give me time to, no!
- Thanks (mumbles).
- [Tom Sirvo] He's the
Lucas Tanner of his time.
He had this meeting with
a bunch of cowboys today,
I think it went pretty
well, you shoulda seen me,
made me honorary chair.
I'm good.
This town needs a Billy
Jack, or a Gabby Hayes,
or a Stretch Armstrong or something.
- This was my idea.
- [Croooow] Flintstone's the movie,
what do you think?
- How long you gonna keep this up?
- As long as they keep stealing my horses.
There's a law against that you know.
- There's also a law about giving a man
a fair trial.
- [Tom Sirvo] No there's not.
- And not shooting him down in cold blood.
- They shouldn't have resisted arrested.
- Resist arrest?
That's just an excuse to legalize murder.
Pete Ferguson didn't
even have a gun on him
when he resisted arrest.
- Just the same, there
were Double C horses
found in their corral.
- I still say a man is innocent
until he's proven guilty.
- [Tom Sirvo] You would think that.
- Call off your deputies.
- [Croooow] Take back your mink
- [Duke] We can settle
this some other way.
- I didn't start this thing Barnum,
but now that it's started,
I'm going to finish it.
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh where's the magic
of that cowboy meeting, damn.
- Is that final?
- That's final.
- [Tom Sirvo] Double dog final.
- Up 'til now there's been
nothing personal about this
on my part.
Here on in, it's gonna be different.
- [Croooow] I'm gonna make
fun of your condition.
- Threats don't scare me any.
See that he gets off the
range without being bothered,
otherwise I'm liable to be
accused of ambushing too.
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh she's
gonna let me see her nude.
- [Mike] More Reba.
(sweet orchestral music)
- [Croooow] Quit dobbing
your neck on my property.
- [Tom Sirvo] Boy my
ears have been dripping
in this windy climate.
(ominous music)
- [Croooow] Ew, I'm not touching it! Yuck!
(sweet orchestral music)
- [Tom Sirvo] Let's have a
merchant ivory sort of picnic,
what do you say?
Well I have to ride back to St. Louis
and get a new hankie.
(sweet orchestral music)
- [Croooow] Could you
uh, pretend I'm not here
and take your hat off?
(chuckles nervously)
- Sorry it had to be this way.
- [Tom Sirvo] I outta shoot ya.
- I know you are.
- But he's wrong and he's got to be shown.
- He's all I have in the world,
I love him in spite of his faults.
- Yes I know.
- [Croooow] You're evil because of it.
- That's why I wanted it to be different.
- [Mike] Hey this feels good tighter.
- Sometimes things don't work out
the way you figured.
- What do you mean?
- Oh a guy will wonder up one range
and down the other always
looking for something
he thinks he can't find.
- [Tom Sirvo] Like a second shirt.
- Then suddenly you'll stop at a spot--
- [Croooow] Oh it's cowboy poetry.
- [Mike] Oh eta Annie.
- I guess I've said more
than I should've already.
- No you haven't Duke.
- [Croooow] Touch my gingham!
- Please go on.
(sweet orchestral music)
- [Croooow] You give me
that nude head of yours.
- [Tom Sirvo] No I can't
be untrue to Remedy.
- [Croooow] So that's it
for my whole life, huh?
- [Tom Sirvo] Yep.
Meanwhile the bandana's out there
like a ticking bomb.
- [Croooow] Every ranch
by strict zoning law
must have parking for these five horses.
- [Tom Sirvo] Did you know that?
- [Mike] I didn't know.
- [Tom Sirvo] Shut up.
- [Croooow] So are you up for some limbo?
Limbo rah ha!
Uh, I wouldn't touch that.
- [Tom Sirvo] Only one man
has this sweaty a neck.
- [Croooow] This movie
should've been called
Lost and Found.
What a luck, you found a hankie,
which I'd found hankie,
I never find anything.
- What's on the program for tonight?
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh Zig Ziggler's in town.
- Hit the Miller ranch.
- But there's been nothing
on his land so far.
- So far, but a couple of Double C horses
found in his corral will
prove him otherwise.
Go pick up Rocky, he's waiting
for you over at the office.
- [Croooow] From zero to one in...
(mumbles)
- Stay where you are!
- [Tom Sirvo] Then again, uh...
- A bit of cover Riley,
but of that you don't have to be clever
to take advantage of
a man in a wheelchair.
- [Tom Sirvo] Don't use
your wheelchair as a crutch.
- I outta kill you two
right where you stand.
- [Mike] Well?
- The right thing to do is to keep you
for the sheriff.
Jane?
- [Mike] Bring boy and cheetah.
- Jane?
- [Tom Sirvo] Jane has you surrounded.
- [Croooow] Uh just as we planned,
Jane doesn't come when I call.
- Jane?
- [Croooow] Oh, could you get that for me?
What I mean is I support your plan,
I wish it many successes.
- Why take it to have it pinned on us.
- [Mr. Cooper] Jane!
(suspenseful music)
Jane!
- [Croooow] Stop this crazy thing!
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh never mind Jane!
- You like the Coopers, don't you?
- [Croooow] Don't you? Dukey
likes his Coopers, doesn't he?
- She's pretty.
- So are you, in a girly sort of way.
- I'm not a girl, I'm
a woman, a grown woman.
- [Tom Sirvo] I'll say.
- What's the matter with you chipmunks?
- Well he...
That is I...
Oh nevermind.
- [Croooow] Well this
moradic acid will be safe,
oh no!
- Why don't you watch where you're going?
- [Tom Sirvo] Uh darn, I've
been saving my own filth
for three weeks, well I just
have to start over again.
Better get to it pal.
- I know it won't do any good, but someday
I'm gonna take a course
in female psychology.
- [Croooow] May even become a female.
(sweet orchestral music)
- [Tom Sirvo] Well dad,
doesn't your anxiety
about my leaving seem silly now.
Better tie it better than
that, I can undo that knot.
I'll leave, I will!
I'm going!
- [Croooow] Oh how sweet dad,
you're taking a little nap on the lawn!
Looks like you got some color dad.
(sweet orchestral music)
- [Tom Sirvo] All right hot wheels,
let's get going.
- [Croooow] Well no time to talk dad,
I'm going straight upstairs.
I have a lot of things to do today.
- Dad, I wanna talk to you.
- [Tom Sirvo] And don't say
I word 'til I'm finished.
- Dad.
- [Mike] Daddy?
- [Tom Sirvo] Dad?
(somber orchestral music)
- [Croooow] Oh good one dad.
- [Tom Sirvo] Thanks a
lot, now I'm an orphan.
- Dad!
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh not
to worry, that was me.
I did that.
You mean you didn't want that done?
(somber orchestral music)
- [Croooow] Man, what a huge ear!
Look at that thing!
- [Tom Sirvo] Now you
apologize to your daughter,
see what you made her do?
Here dry your tears with
this clue I planted.
- [Croooow] Oh geez, how
long is she gonna mourn?
- [Tom Sirvo] It's not
so much that he's dead,
it's just that I have this headache.
- I've seen this bandana before.
It belongs to Duke Barnum.
- [Tom Sirvo] See the neck sweat?
- No, no he couldn't.
- Why not?
- I was with him.
I was at the edge of the range with him.
- After he left you, he
must've circled back here.
- [Croooow] Come on,
it's my plan, play along.
- He could've made it back
before you did, couldn't he?
- [Tom Sirvo] Anyway,
it smells like Anteus,
that's his scent.
(mumbles)
- That settles it.
I'm going after the sheriff.
- [Croooow] I better put dad up on blocks
and leave him in the garage.
- [Tom Sirvo] Baby. Geez.
(upbeat pop music)
(growls erupt)
- [Mike] Would you settle down?
Get outta here.
- Is this yours?
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh boy, who'd I kill now?
- Yeah thanks, I must've
dropped it somewhere.
- Over at the Double C maybe?
- Could be, why?
- It'll probably hang you.
- [Croooow] Wow, they have really strict
littering laws around here.
- [Mike] When horse has
a beatle's (mumbles).
- You're under arrest for
the murder of Charlie Cooper.
- [Tom Sirvo] Johnny Pooper? Who's that?
♫ Johnny Pooper, number
two bad man in the west ♫
(chuckles)
- [Croooow] Johnny Pooper, also murdered,
killed in his own log cabin.
(cackles)
- [Tom Sirvo] Good one!
Flash, attractive woman spotted!
- [Croooow] Pooper held as probe widens.
(chuckles)
Barnum hires midgets for defense team.
- [Tom Sirvo] Jumbo to be
witness for prosecution.
- [Croooow] Rose Kennedy
celebrates jubilee.
(chuckles)
Kanishes, get your old west kanishes.
- [Tom Sirvo] Yep, you can get
watch a wagon wheel get made
or we can go to the trial.
- [Croooow] It's crowd
noise days in Jacksonville,
the milling about festival.
- Looks like the whole town
turned out for the trial.
- [Croooow] Should've made t-shirts.
(mumbles)
- No, there ain't a lawyer in the county
wants to touch the case.
- Well what will we do?
- Looks like I got to try to defend him,
I had a little law training.
- Do you think you can?
- I'll do my best.
Prosecutor's built up a powerful case.
- [Tom Sirvo] Shut up.
(inaudible mumbles)
Here a group was lodge uptight.
Pooper can get him loose.
Hey a call back a distance
for the Marlboro man.
- [Croooow] That was a good AA meeting.
Why would anyone be sober in this town?
- I'll see you inside.
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh crack hits the old west.
- [Croooow] That guy on the
far left, nice curvy butt.
(mumbles)
- You've been doing a
lot of drinking lately.
What's a matter, losing your nerve?
- I can't help it.
- [Croooow] I'm Irish.
- [Tom Sirvo] Good one.
(mumbles)
- This one got me.
- [Tom Sirvo] Down drugs
and self gig, (burps).
- Keep seeing that old man sitting there
in his wheelchair.
- You need to take a trip, a long one.
- [Croooow] I know a guy, ask Mr. Foster,
tell him I sent you.
- [Tom Sirvo] Here, go drink some more.
- And don't come back this way.
- [Tom Sirvo] You are a beautiful man,
everybody is this is a beautiful man.
- [Croooow] Have a good time.
- Do you all understand?
- [Mike] Sure, you guys know him?
Anybody know him?
(gasps out)
- [Tom Sirvo] So why'd they have the trial
on the 48th floor?
- [Voiceover] You're employed as a guard
by the expense company, are you not?
- [Croooow] Guilty!
- [Tom Sirvo] Not yet.
- [Croooow] Oh sorry.
- On July 10th while riding a stage coach
into Jacksonville...
- [Tom Sirvo] You mean July?
- You reported seeing a
masked man on the road
through a pair of field
glasses, is that right?
- That's right, I saw him
through field glasses.
- [Croooow] I was cowboy watching.
- Stand up, put your hat on.
- [Croooow] Now go stand 250 yards away.
- [Tom Sirvo] Pst, wanna
get sequestered later?
- Oh wait a minute,
that ain't got anything
to do with the case, so I object.
- I'm only trying to
establish the character
of the defendant, your honor.
- Objection overruled,
answer the question,
is that the man?
(barks erupt)
- [Croooow] So I think he's color's done.
- Yes.
- [Tom Sirvo] Would
you say the man you saw
is a winter?
- [Croooow] Please hold your applause
until all the testimony has been given.
- By the first day he hit
this spot of the country,
he shot one of the Double C men.
- [Tom Sirvo] Semen, semen.
(chuckles)
Semen.
- [Mike] Thank you, thank
you, it was me, I did it,
thank you...
- [Croooow] Keep the
faith honey, he's dead.
(crowd chatters)
- Duke Barnum has been a troublemaker
every since he arrived.
- [Tom Sirvo] Your bottom
has been a troublemaker?
- He's repeatedly attacked my men
without any provocation.
(crowd protests)
- [Croooow] It's too
chilly for this (mumbles).
- [Voiceover] Order, order.
- Did the defendant, Duke Barnum,
ever threaten your
father in your presence?
- [Tom Sirvo] Take the
curtain, the curtain.
- [Croooow] Hey witness, hey!
She's a perjur, hey witness!
- [Tom Sirvo] Yeah, no, it's maybe, yes.
- Yes.
(crowd grumbles)
Now he'll like me!
- [Croooow] Maybe I am guilty.
- [Tom Sirvo] We will not sing
a mighty fortress is our God.
- What is the jury's verdict?
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh we weren't
listening your honor.
- Guilty your honor.
(crowd gasps)
- [Croooow] Wait, they didn't
say I specifically was guilty.
- [Tom Sirvo] I'm deputy dog.
- [Croooow] Hey deputy dog.
- [Tom Sirvo] You've been a lousy client.
- [Croooow] Here's that gun you want.
(whispered mumbles)
- Come on sheriff, get going.
- [Tom Sirvo] Okay, there'll
be a 10 minute break
and the next sensational trial will begin.
(crowd panics)
- [Croooow] 12 pansy men.
(hums whimsically)
- [Tom Sirvo] Hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey!
- [Croooow] That's a warehouse in Newark.
- [Tom Sirvo] I know hold it, hold it,
I've always wanted to do this.
- [Croooow] Ow!
- [Tom Sirvo] That saved
all of two seconds.
- Come out, let's get him.
- [Croooow] Can I get a ride with you Ted?
- [Tom Sirvo] Ah, life is so hard
when you're stupid.
(chuckles)
- I wonder how that coulda happened?
- [Tom Sirvo] Remedy, you're
a national freaking treasure.
- I wonder.
(laughter erupts)
- There aren't many places he an hide out.
- [Croooow] That's Hitchcock.
- I want him brought in.
- [Croooow] First they were mad,
but then they had to
admit it was pretty funny.
- [Tom Sirvo] Should just close this down
and start over.
- If you'd rather go back before,
just proves that he's guilty.
- [Croooow] Dr. Quinn,
frontier proctologist.
Isn't anybody following me?
I thought I was a big important criminal?
- [Tom Sirvo] I dunno,
it just feels like I forgot something.
- [Croooow] Sir, why
don't you put the gun away
before someone gets hurt.
- [Tom Sirvo] Where's
of territory I wonder.
Well heck, I'll just keep
going the way I was going.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Croooow] I coulda caught your higher,
but no, I go with Remedy.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
Huh, procrastinating beaver, do you see?
Come on Duke, have you done your business?
- Did Remedy get back yet?
- [Remedy] Duke!
- Don't worry it's Remedy.
- [Croooow] But kill him anyway.
- They're searching every
ranch in the valley,
they're headed this way now.
You best be moving on Duke.
- Where to?
- Wait a minute, there's
an old cave up the hills
overlooking the pass, I used to hide there
when I was a little girl.
I don't think anybody knows about it.
I'll take you there.
- No, no, you've done enough.
(mumbles)
How do I get there?
- Well, you cut across the
south end of Cookoo Ranch.
- [Tom Sirvo] Wait, I'm lost, start again.
- Follow that for about
a mile, and then...
- [Tom Sirvo] About a mile...
- [Croooow] And then you
get shot by these guys.
(mumbles)
I got a slipped disk, oh!
(horse gallops)
There goes the dumbest
cowboy you'll ever meet.
- [Tom Sirvo] Where should I bill you?
- [Mike] It's the (mumbles).
- We're looking for Duke
Barnum, have you seen him?
- [Remedy] Oh he was around here--
- There he is!
(metal clangs)
- Okay, alternate universe manual.
- Suppose we should read the introduction?
- Yeah.
- So you die captain and
we all move up in rank.
- You don't not, get outta here.
- Welcome to the world
of alternate universes.
- Crew has orders to kill you captain.
(chuckles evilly)
And he will succeed apparently,
regrettable, but it will
leave me in command,
then I will exploit
the dilithium crystal--
- Sirvo!
- I can't wait to get
him back to his universe,
a little annoying.
- You take a lot of chances.
Doh!
(static buzzes)
- Don't consider me for your
next corporate function,
I'm available for all sorts of events.
- Look, enough with Joey the Lemur.
(hums whimsically)
(groans out)
- You know, this just might
be an alternate universe.
- Well duh!
Maybe they got a computer down here.
- Yeah, he, computer?
- [Voiceover] Working.
- That one sounds like Torko.
- [Voiceover] Oh?
- Hey computer.
- [Voiceover] Working.
- Say the master.
- [Voiceover] The master.
- That's great, it sounds exactly like--
- Tom!
- What?
Oh right, our computer, are
we in an alternate universe?
- [Voiceover] Yes.
- Well how do we get out?
- [Voiceover] Uh, yeah, frank and course
to send back the matter
transference device.
- Say the master again.
- Play that order!
Computer, would you
put Frank and Forrester
on the screen please?
- Oh right, remember,
you're the evil Gypsy.
- Oh lord, I don't know if I can...
Lord, they're still singing
that Joey the Lemur song.
Hey you knuckleheads,
send down that matter
transference machine.
♫ We the lemur ♫
- Oh sure!
♫ Joey the lemur, he really is great
♫ Joey ♫
(air swooshes)
(electronic tones buzz)
(gasps out)
- Wow.
Okay, all right, all
right, everybody here?
Nobody evil? Gypsy?
- Not evil.
- I'm still not convinced it happened.
- Perhaps it ended on potato,
or a bit of undigested beef.
- Fine Scrooge, let's check on the mads.
- Okay.
(groans out)
- I feel so strange, it's as if
all my intestines cried out at once
and were suddenly silenced.
Oh, but Frank! Look!
Someone left us an agony booth.
- Me first!
- Race ya!
- [Frank] Let me in there, get!
(upbeat pop music)
- [Mike] Now I for one
am glad you're back.
- [Tom Sirvo] Me too.
Wonder what's happened?
(somber orchestral music)
- [Croooow] She didn't have someone
haul away dad I suppose.
Hey it's the guy who
killed dad, yoohoo, yoohoo!
(ominous music)
Oh mother blob!
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh you got
some of my tapes I think,
yeah I think you got (mumbles).
(gun shot fires)
- [Croooow] We got a domestic in progress
over at the old Pooper place.
I love you!
(gun shot fires)
What is it about you?
I don't need an answer right away.
Her bullets say no, but
her eyes say come hither.
- [Mike] Strange courting
practices of the old west.
- [Tom Sirvo] Shut up.
- [Croooow] So I can't use your bathroom?
- Jane!
It's me Duke!
- I know that.
- [Croooow] Oh!
- Stand where you are and drop your gun.
- But Jane, I...
(gun shot fires)
- [Croooow] Oh women.
(sorrowful orchestral music)
- [Tom Sirvo] Geez I'm having a bad day.
- [Croooow] Well that's
dating the 90s, the 1890s.
(laughter erupts)
It's not fair, she had a bigger gun.
- [Mike] You know what? I'm
really not that mad at him.
- [Croooow] Never brides,
always bridesmaids.
(sweet orchestral music)
Now he's Log Ogleby.
(chuckles)
Log? (mumbles)
- [Tom Sirvo] Everything's
up to date in Kansas City.
- Remedy, Duke's not at the cave,
it didn't look he'd been there either.
- Probably couldn't find it in the dark.
I think I'll get some guys
and see what I can find out.
- [Croooow] You sure this
will make good toilet paper?
- If you wait 'til my
cake raises, I'll go too.
- [Tom Sirvo] (mumbles) western style.
Syd!
- [All] El Syd!
- [Tom Sirvo] Syd!
(sweet orchestral music)
(mumbles)
- [Croooow] Go away, nobody likes me.
Emerald City is closed!
(ominous music)
- [Tom Sirvo] He's hiding
in an abandoned stuckies.
(chuckles)
- [Mike] This shot's just screaming out
for a huge grass hopper to appear.
- [Croooow] Everybody is so stupid,
he could just go into
town with a fake mustache
and no one would notice.
- [Tom Sirvo] Well that's
not my force, I'm not here!
Go away!
- [Mike] Lucky, this hideout
sometimes is real crowded.
- [Croooow] This place is such a mess,
he should clean up his hideout.
(mumbles)
- Oh it's not too bad, just a flesh wound.
- [Tom Sirvo] Touch it.
- Oh I'll clean it up,
then I'll go get Remedy.
Soon as it gets dark,
we'll get you out of here.
- Well I've been thinking about that.
- [Tom Sirvo] Go lower!
- I wanna stay here.
This is the last place in the world
they'd think of looking for me.
♫ Doo lee, doo lee, doo lee ♫
- [Croooow] He's in here!
Yuck.
- Stuff makes me sneeze,
hay fever I guess.
- Remedy must have a remedy for that,
I'll bring you some back.
- [Croooow] Great scene, huh?
(chuckles)
- [Mike] Geez, this movie has more scenes
of people picking at themselves.
(chuckles)
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh just doing
a little morning bowl,
then get to work.
(inhales sharply)
- [Croooow] No, you can't have any,
this is $80 an ounce.
(inhales sharply)
- [Mike] He should just
put a towel under the door.
- [Tom Sirvo] So you wanna
walk across the street
to Fenway and catch a game?
- Rocky tells me that my
men are no longer deputies.
- [Croooow] Again?
- That's right Riley, the
way things have quieted down
with Double C, you don't need anymore.
- [Croooow] Nice to back your own,
is that field and stream?
- What about Duke Barnum?
- Oh we can handle him when we catch him.
- I take it my boys could help you out.
- [Tom Sirvo] Would you stop
touching yourself there?
- Riley?
- [Croooow] This could be the start
of a beautiful friendship.
- Duke Barnum was convicted legally,
and he's gonna hang legally too,
but I aim to see that
he's brought in alive.
- [Tom Sirvo] You pot head.
Go listen to some big bamboo huh?
- [Croooow] Oh well,
rotator cuff feels good,
I think I'll be ready
for my start on Thursday.
- [Voiceover] It's me again.
- Who are you yesterday?
- [Tom Sirvo] I brought
you some swaddling clothes.
- (mumbles) get off this ranch.
- [Croooow] And my purse, thank you!
- [Tom Sirvo] Wanna play some marbles?
- (mumbles) beginning to
get on my nerves I guess.
- Oh another day or two and
you'll be as good as new.
(sneezes forcefully)
- [Croooow] Oh green sleeves.
(chuckles)
- You better bring me
a facial pile of pills.
- I'll pick 'em up in town tomorrow
when I go for my mail.
- What's been going on?
- Well this Cooper thing sorta put an end
to all that fighting.
- [Croooow] The coy remedy.
- [Tom Sirvo] I just feel that
can't leave a brown mustard.
- [Croooow] A priest and a rabbi walk...
- Riley Morgan took
over the Ferguson ranch,
the Andrews ranch, and three other places.
- [Croooow] Well you
probably outta get going.
- You've picked up some notes at the bank.
- [Croooow] Notes?
- Dead man's notes.
- Yeah I know what you mean,
but we ain't got no proof.
- [Croooow] You ever done it in the hay?
(mumbles)
My crotch is suddenly cold.
Okay.
- How are you Remedy?
(mumbles)
This stuff sure (mumbles).
- [Tom Sirvo] Especially
when you don't deliver it.
- Oh let me know when
you go to the Double C.
- Oh why?
- Drop this letter off for Riley Morgan,
save me a trip.
- Sure!
- [Tom Sirvo] If you don't,
I might become disgruntled.
♫ Bless this beautiful day ♫
- [Croooow] It's a
letter, it doesn't rattle.
(sweet orchestral music)
- [Tom Sirvo] Let's see here,
dear sir, your horse has a
potentially serious design flaw
that could result in explosion and fire.
(sweet orchestral music)
- [Croooow] Eh Betty some morphine,
Jack will have the bike
killed, Casper Doodle.
- [Tom Sirvo] The US Post
Office, there's still
no cheaper way to deliver
a blackmail threat.
- [Mike] Hi it's general delivery,
one of the great general's
of the Civil War.
- [Croooow] Ah he's covering the stamp
so he can't see that
it has Roosevelt on it.
- [Mike] So I get three free CDs now?
(horses gallop)
(ominous music)
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh geez, they should
call this movie Butterfingers.
- [Croooow] What is the point?
(rapid orchestral music)
Ungodly coincidences of the old west.
- He dropped something, see what it is.
- [Croooow] It's a plot device,
it's very flimsy so be careful.
(chuckles)
- Just a couple of letters.
- [Tom Sirvo] I'll just
read 'em with my feet.
- Hey this one's for you,
it's from Hank Davis.
- [Mike] Oh I don't know any Hank Davis,
let me see that.
(ominous music)
- [Croooow] Guilty
Valley, Guilty California.
(ominous orchestral music)
- [Mike] Oh shoot, there
was probably gum in here,
he always sends me some.
- Come on, I want that letter.
- [Tom Sirvo] We'll head
him off at exit 31C.
- [Croooow] (whines) I don't wanna see
another horse chase!
(suspenseful orchestral music)
(imitates gallops musically)
Stop it!
I didn't read the letter, go away!
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Tom Sirvo] That's it,
I'm going to Vodville.
(imitates gallops musically)
- [Croooow] Let's see,
what's the stupidest thing
I could do?
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh he's got one
of them amphibious horses.
- [Croooow] This is no
place for a gelding.
- [Mike] Or maybe they're like bees
and they won't go in the water.
Sure enough!
(upbeat pop music)
- Wait.
Wait until he gets in the middle,
it couldn't be fair.
- [Croooow] I'm on ghoul!
- [Mike] Watch this, right in the butt.
(gun shot fires)
- [Tom Sirvo] Fortunately, Remedy's taken
a correspondence scuba course.
- [Croooow] And a little
bit of Jacksonville
died that day.
- He was anxious to get somewhere,
I got a pretty good hunch
what was in that letter,
but it's where no one will see it now,
except maybe fishes.
- [Tom Sirvo] I'm sick of your carping.
- I think you and I better ride
over to Red Bluff next week and fix Hank
so that he doesn't write any more letters.
- [Croooow] But I thought
we were gonna have
our captain holiday.
(ominous orchestral music)
- [Mike] People just
wander from scene to scene
in this movie.
- [Croooow] Sanson, see!
- [Tom Sirvo] I see it!
- [Croooow] Solar panels.
(sorrowful music)
- [Mike] Let's make a statement
with a roof in this design.
- [Tom Sirvo] Wisconsin
and that barn would say
diesel cheese gifts.
(chuckles)
- [Croooow] Early car hops.
- [Tom Sirvo] Where's my bear honey?
I thought you were Dell.
- Now you shouldn't come here too often,
somebody might see.
- Well I had to take
care of Remedy's patient.
- [Tom Sirvo] And I need
the child support payment.
- Look, you've got to get out of here,
if they find you, they'll kill you.
- I can't keep hiding forever,
besides if I leave, I'll
never prove anything.
- [Croooow] What does he just sit in there
and plan golf courses in his mind?
- [Mike] Boy you just sit
back and they roll right in.
Ah, pretend she's not here.
- I have a horse saddle
that's waiting for you
as soon as it gets dark.
- [Croooow] Would you like corn bread
or coleslaw with that?
- You mean you'd help me get away?
- Yes.
- [Tom Sirvo] I wanna french your hat.
- I'd never leave knowing you'd think
I killed your father.
- Look you've got to.
- [Tom Sirvo] But I killed your father.
- Terry's right, they'll kill you.
Somehow I feel you're innocent
and I'll never forgive myself.
- [Croooow] The mummy!
(gasps out)
- Remedy!
- [Tom Sirvo] Worse!
- [Croooow] Bull hat's got me!
(mumbles)
- [Tom Sirvo] Is it wrong
that I'm glad about this?
- [Mike] You know, I think those women
did the right thing by
not wearing earrings
with those outfits.
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh we're accessorizing.
- [Croooow] Ew, he blew
his nose on that thing,
get rid of it!
- [Mike] Take the juice of two lemons...
What is this?
- Take this to the sheriff.
You stay here with him.
- [Croooow] Oh thank you, I'll babysit
the wet bloody stinky Remedy.
(rapid orchestral music)
(imitates gallops musically)
If the horse drops below
50, it will explode.
- [Mike] Speed, woo!
- [Tom Sirvo] Well Syd's making good time!
- Come on, I'll buy you a drink.
- [Mike] Oh, let me call Ripley's.
(chuckles)
- [Croooow] Hey, I'm not
guilty everyone, get him!
Kill him, get him!
- [Tom Sirvo] An old
tom town looks the same.
- [Croooow] Ah Jacksonville.
Hey, he changed his
shirt, must be a disguise.
- [Tom Sirvo] Don't
think of that, don't...
- [Croooow] Ching, ching, ching, ching.
(cracks tongue)
Ching, ching...
- [Mike] Not even time for a quick scotch?
- [Croooow] I hope he kills
the apple dumpling gang.
(chuckles)
- [Mike] What's that thing you say, grab!
- [Tom Sirvo] No.
- [Mike] Push.
- [Duke] We know who killed
Charlie Cooper, Riley.
- [Tom Sirvo] Who's Charlie Cooper Riley?
Now you know what I meant.
- But I'm settling a
personal matter first.
- [Croooow] Got a package to
pick up over at the Sears.
(gun shots fire)
Get off me you load.
Hey he never got his drink.
- [Tom Sirvo] Hey, wait,
I wanted to tell you
who killed that guy,
this is the funny part,
it was you!
(chuckles)
Hey, geez, when a man's gotta go.
- [Croooow] There's a
Hooverville in this town.
- [Tom Sirvo] Hey!
(chuckles)
It's the last straw.
- [Mike] Oh where do you want it?
(ominous orchestral music)
- [Croooow] You're too late,
I have an informal agreement
with the owners.
- [Tom Sirvo] You're mad aren't you?
I can tell you're mad.
- [Mike] Uh just don't tickle me,
I'm thin and it wouldn't be fair.
(chuckles)
- That door's the only way out of here.
- That's brave talk for a man with a gun.
- [Croooow] Hey, I'm just
telling you where the door is,
just kinda FYI, no reason
to get all mad at me.
- That's right Riley.
- [Tom Sirvo] Yep.
- Well I'll give you a better break
than you gave Cooper and Remedy.
(rapid orchestral music)
- [Tom Sirvo] I'll give you
the first seven punches,
kicks too!
- [Croooow] We already saw this,
so can we be excused?
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Mike] We want out.
- [Croooow] Albert Casser wanted
to do his best work for this scene
and unfortunately he did.
- [Mike] A comfortable
place for a fight anyway.
- [Tom Sirvo] You'll do anything to get me
into leather, won't you?
- [Croooow] So do they all
him western saddles back then?
- [Tom Sirvo] I suppose.
- [Mike] Oh please, I've
already got hay in my pants.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Tom Sirvo] Away and a murder,
no crib for a death, the cattle are dying.
- [Croooow] Hey Poncho, hey Cisco.
(chuckles)
- [Tom Sirvo] Would you two keep the fight
on the lower level?
We're filming our way from it up here.
- [Croooow] I still hope they kill
the apple dumpling gang.
(chuckles)
The air's thinner up here,
so I think that means
the skinny guy has an advantage.
- [Tom Sirvo] And smell it, smell my hand.
- [Crooook] He's Baron Von Rashky.
Oh found my needle.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
See?
This proves you did it!
- [Tom Sirvo] This is
about than just murder
and blackmail between these two women.
- [Mike] Just think,
right now the townspeople
are getting uglier, stupider,
and they're dropping things.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Croooow] You know,
this scene disturbed me
at the beginning of the movie,
but now it makes me happy.
- You never shoulda butted into this
in the first place Barnum,
now I'm going to finish you.
(whip cracks)
(ominous orchestral music)
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh he's gonna keep
a little blood mustache.
- [Mike] Usually when
this guy kills people,
he makes them go get the belt.
- [Croooow] Humiliating.
(hums whimsically)
(yelps out)
- [Mike] They fell off the hashbrowns.
- [Croooow] Oh I had a huge skeleton key
in my front pocket, owie.
(groans out)
No, stay here, I'll make us breakfast.
- [Tom Sirvo] Tu es incroyable, partner.
That's it, that's French partner.
- [Croooow] Oh that didn't help.
Now the bowling ball's
gonna roll down on his head!
(chuckles)
- [Tom Sirvo] I fought
the loft and the loft won.
- [Mike] Oh man, sorry it's Colleen.
- [Croooow] Well everything's better now.
Doc said my spine just healed right up,
it was amazing.
- Hi Terry!
- [Croooow] You're dirt!
- Hi Jane!
- How's the patient?
- Well he's been swell up until today,
look at him now.
- [Tom Sirvo] It's McGreets.
(chuckles)
- That's some fancy
looking suit he's wearing.
- He won't tell me why, but he brought
his suit for the day.
- [Croooow] Getting
shot was the best thing
that ever happened to him.
- Hello Remedy.
- [Tom Sirvo] I'm not reading Hustler.
- Another mail order court?
- Well I had to do
something while I was laying
on my back for two months.
- What kind of a course
is it this time Remedy?
- You'll see, are you men getting in?
(mumbles)
- [Mike] Remedy is now
completely psychotic.
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh the Well's Fargo wagon
is a coming down the street.
(playful orchestral music)
- [Croooow] I have to go
to the long park bank.
- [Tom Sirvo] We're spreading the word
of no sex or alcohol.
(playful orchestral music)
It's Stalin with Svetlana.
- [Croooow] Well at least Curly
won't have to wear a dress anymore.
- This came for you today Remedy.
- [Tom Sirvo] Oh no.
- [Croooow] This?
(chuckles)
- [Mike] This is really creepy.
- I'm taking a mail order course now,
this lesson calls for a model, (mumbles).
- [Tom Sirvo] Dad, please protect me.
- [Croooow] Remedy, there are laws.
(playful orchestral music)
- So long Curly.
- I wonder how they--
- [Mike] Oh ram it clown.
(laughter erupts)
- [Tom Sirvo] Yes, let's
close with another random
assortment of notes,
courtesy of Albert Glass.
(drums whimscally)
(metal clangs)
- Mike, would you mind
telling me what happened?
- Yeah.
- Well sure, you see the mads,
sent up the matter transference device
during an ion storm,
dumb thing to do, right?
Yeah, 'cause it sent Tom Sirvo
and our own lovable Gypsy
into an alternate universe
whilst your evil dopplegangers
were sent into ours.
- Oh is that all it was?
You know gang, I think
about one trip a year
to an alternate universe is enough for me.
(laughter erupts)
It wasn't that funny, was it?
- No, no sir.
That's all right, let's read this letter
that might (mumbles).
- Hi guys!
- Oh hi!
- Say Frank and I figured out a way
that we can communicate from our side
of light of love to your
side of light of love,
so we thought we'd stop by and say hi.
- [All] Hi!
- As a matter of fact, we've prepared
a little song for you.
We hope you like it, it goes
a little something like this.
♫ Joey the lemur ♫
(mumbles)
- Hate to stop ya, hate to stop ya,
hate like the world to do it,
we have to read a letter.
(mumbles)
Or we get punished or something--
- Yeah we get punished.
- So anyway, here it is.
It's from Joseph A. Hotlzman,
and we put on Seal Store can I?
Joseph's from Kailua, Hawaii.
- Ah, yes in our world,
we also have a Hawaii
and many similar places.
Your Massachusetts, your Illinois,
your (speaks foreign language)--
- Yeah that's great, the letter begins,
dear Mike and the bots,
we really enjoy your show
on oceanic cable channel 30--
- Ah yes!
In our world, we too have cable television
where we enjoy many
similar programs to yours,
your I Love Lucy, your Home Improvement,
your My Mother the Collasal
Colloosta Collasta Calleekie--
- Yeah I'll bet you let it go.
Letter concludes by saying, anyway,
keep up the riffs--
- Ah yes!
In our world, we too have riffs.
We listen to many forms of popular music
such as your Louis
Armstrong, your The Beatles,
your Zyloc Blues Band from
Omicron Steady Three, your--
- Well we're sorry, I have to go!
(inaudible chatter)
Bye bye!
(whistles)
Wow, in a way really, it's
kinda comforting to know
that no matter what universe you're from,
you can still be really annoying.
- Amen to that!
- Yeah.
(groans out painfully)
(static buzzes)
(playful synthesizer music)
(laughs boisterously)